<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OSR October</title><link>https://main--sweet-figolla-586142.netlify.app/</link><description>Recent content on OSR October</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 18:18:26 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://main--sweet-figolla-586142.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Real Arnosto</title><link>https://main--sweet-figolla-586142.netlify.app/posts/therealarnosto/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 18:18:26 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://main--sweet-figolla-586142.netlify.app/posts/therealarnosto/</guid><description>It is not quite October yet, but I need to warm up a little and I am moving my character sheet to this blog so that I can maintain it in GitHub and have it available all the time and wherever I am.
The Real Arnosto is a Fighter/Magic User/Werewolf. Say that three times quickly.
Classes Fighter/Magic User Background Weaver Alignment Neutral Levels 2/1 Statistics AC I don&amp;rsquo;t know, have to look at notes XP 4,920 HP 10/10 Ability Scores STRength 13 INTelligence 11 WISdom 8 DEXterity 11 CONstitution 11 CHArisma 10 Saving Throws Death, Poison 12 Wands 13 Paralysis, Petrify 13 Breath Attcks 15 Spells, Rods, Staves 16 Skills and Abilities Melee: +1 on attack and damage Open Stuck Doors: 3/6 Retainers Max: 4 Loyalty: 7 Equipment SpellBook Features and Traits Treasure Gold Silver Copper 000 000 000 Rope 50ft Rations 00 days Background Weaver, need to fill this in.</description></item><item><title>How To</title><link>https://main--sweet-figolla-586142.netlify.app/posts/how-to/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 17:38:26 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://main--sweet-figolla-586142.netlify.app/posts/how-to/</guid><description>Next October, the chances of me remembering how to use this are pretty slim. So:
look to see if I have the repo github.com/danroscigno/darvas cloned to /home/droscigno/GitHub/darvas/
git pull if it is there, or clone it if it is missing Start a Golang container (I don&amp;rsquo;t have any luck with Golang, so I run it in a container. Same with Python. Probably has nothing to do with my ability to run these, and everything to do with incompatible versions.</description></item><item><title>My OSR story</title><link>https://main--sweet-figolla-586142.netlify.app/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 01:27:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://main--sweet-figolla-586142.netlify.app/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>My OSR story Although I am of the correct age to have been a player of Chainmail and the subsequent games, I never played until about 2019. I had some exposure in the 80s as one of my roommates played, but I was about to get married, and although I bought some books at the time, I never played.
My first game was a D&amp;amp;D Adventurers Leage1 game at Atomic Empire2 in Durham, NC.</description></item></channel></rss>